<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weak Ontology</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 20:15:55 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 20:15:55 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.3</generator>

    
      <item>
        <title>Learning in Circles</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Ayo dis ting work?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vix dico eius nominati cu, ex zril commodo fuisset mea. Habeo adhuc audiam ius no. In quis virtute officiis has. Vix ad honestatis accommodare, quis virtute et sit, pertinax expetenda eam id. Duo an fuisset delectus dissentias, justo altera ea per.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;todo&quot;&gt;Todo&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Duis id ante elit. Aliquam quis tellus id orci eleifend finibus. Donec consequat justo ligula, eget sodales purus hendrerit at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ut at interdum nunc. Maecenas commodo turpis quis elementum gravida.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nunc ac sapien tellus. Quisque risus enim, tempus eget porttitor in, pellentesque vel urna.
 Donec nibh massa, rutrum a sollicitudin eu,
lacinia in lorem.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;graphic-design&quot;&gt;Graphic design&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Graphic design is the paradise of individuality, eccentricity, heresy, abnormality, hobbies, and humors. - George Santayana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vim te case nihil oblique, has partem interpretaris ne, ad admodum accusamus nam. Usu utinam dissentias referrentur ne, vim accusam voluptua pertinacia no. Est no posse utinam inermis, brute errem mentitum et ius, te prompta albucius quo. In pro simul soleat regione.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1433785567155-bf5530cab72c?ixlib=rb-0.3.5&amp;amp;q=80&amp;amp;fm=jpg&amp;amp;crop=entropy&amp;amp;w=1080&amp;amp;fit=max&amp;amp;s=1348aea714b9493fa61a09a8c01113e6&quot; alt=&quot;alt&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ne reque offendit singulis mea, ad eos ferri doming nostrud. Duis suscipit usu ut, fuisset pericula ex est, et porro prompta his. Audire definiebas voluptatibus et duo, aperiam ocurreret ad nec. Vel ad nostrud principes. Ad liber congue iracundia sed, eirmod erroribus eam te, has veniam epicurei ea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pri probo alterum aliquando an. Duo appetere laboramus intellegat ea, ex suas diam exerci vix. Mel simul debitis id, est nusquam fuisset mentitum in. Te mei iudico iisque.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/Learning-in-Circles</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/Learning-in-Circles</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You've been Tinderstruck</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-size:0.9em&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dating apps are certainly not the devil, but they’re still far from an optimal solution. Being successful on those apps is a numbers game and it can all be broken down into small conversational templates you can switch between and track. Scripted interactions can easily get boring and counterproductive.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to establish right from the get-go that I have no intention on shitting on dating apps and I’m certainly not going to moralize on how Tinder is the devil’s work and how people should meet in the real world like they’re supposed to. There’s a time and a place for dating apps and they’ve already proven their instrumental value more than enough to be questioned on that point. That being said, the basic mechanism of online dating imposes various functional bottlenecks that can significantly reduce the chances of some users’ success (however defined).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;context-is-everything&quot;&gt;Context is everything&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think about yourself. You are a complex collection of memories, attitudes and personal quirks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matches are rarely seen as human beings (this goes for both men and women)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;conversational-judo-is-fun&quot;&gt;Conversational judo is fun&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;scripts-are-boring&quot;&gt;Scripts are boring&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;####&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/Youve-been-Tinderstruck</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/Youve-been-Tinderstruck</guid>
      </item>
    

    
      
        
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    

  </channel>
</rss>